Gabrielson, Guy George; Papers apap248
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Guy Gabrielson Papers
1925-1967
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Gabrielson, Guy George, 1891-1976
apap248
5.5 cubic ft. 1 Digital Files
The Guy Gabrielson Papers contain materials that document the political career of Guy George Gabrielson from his start in New Jersey state politics through his years as Chairman of the Republican National Committee. Many of the materials document the 1952 U.S. Presidential election and Republican National Committee Convention which Gabrielson presided over as chairman.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
Syracuse University received the papers of Guy George Gabrielson in a series of acquisitions in 1965 and 1967 and subsequently transferred them to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2006.
Biographical Sketch
Guy George Gabrielson was born in Sioux Rapids, Iowa in May 1891. He received a bachelor of arts degree from the University of Iowa in 1914 and a law degree from Harvard University in 1917. From 1917-1919 he served as a private in the U.S. Army. His political career began in 1925 as a Republican member of the General Assembly of New Jersey from Essex County; in 1929 he became the General Assemblys Speaker of the House. He became the Executive Director of the New Jersey State Campaign in 1936 and its chairman in 1940. Gabrielson was a member of the Republican National Committee (RNC) from 1944-1952 and RNC Chairman from 1949-1952. In 1951 he was involved in a loan scandal that prompted Senator Richard Nixon to call for his removal as chairman. Gabrielson left the RNC in 1952 and returned to practicing law. He later became acting chief executive and president of the John Wood Company of New York and chairman of the Nichold Company of Delaware. Gabrielson died in May of 1976 in Point Pleasant, New Jersey, preceded in death by his wife Cora. The couple had two children.
Gabrielson is best known for his work as chairman of the RNC. In 1952 he opened the convention that nominated General Dwight D. Eisenhower for president. Gabrielson was a controversial figure at the convention; his support of Ohio Senator Robert Taft for the presidential nomination offended backers of Eisenhower who believed that Gabrielson was using his privileges as party chairman to promote the candidacy of Senator Taft.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials that document the political career of Guy George Gabrielson from his start in New Jersey state politics through his years as chairman of the Republican National Committee (RNC). It includes correspondence, documents pertaining to official RNC events, official statements from Gabrielson as RNC chairman, a scrapbook of news clippings from his early political career, correspondence, photographs, various material documenting the operations of the RNC such as state elections and regional conferences. The largest part of the collection consists of files related to the 1952 RNC national convention.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - Early Political Career, 1925-1944, Undated
Series 2 - Republican National Committee Papers, 1948-1967, Undated
Series 3 - Republican National Committee 1952 Convention, 1948-1956, Undated
Series are arranged alphabetically.
Public Servants; Politicians--Washington (D.C.); Campaign literature--United States; Presidents--United States--Election--1940; Presidents--United States--Election--1952; Washington (D.C.)--Politics and government; Essex County (N.J.); Chicago (Ill.); Clippings; Correspondence; Photographs; Speeches; Brochures; Minutes; Memorabilia; Agendas (administrative records); Files by subject; Digital Files; Gabrielson, Guy George, 1891-1976; Taft, Robert Alphonso, 1889-1953; Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969; Willkie, Wendell L. (Wendell Lewis), 1892-1944; Republican National Committee (U.S.); Republican National Committee (U.S.)--Congresses; Republican Party (Essex County, N.J.); Republican Party (N.J.); Republican National Convention
- Early Political Career, 1925-1944; 1
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains a scrapbook of news clippings from Guy George Gabrielsons early political career in New Jersey state government (1925-1940), materials related to his role as the chairman of the New Jersey Campaign Committee for U.S. presidential candidate Wendell Willkie, additional news clippings related to New Jersey Republican political activities, rules and resolutions of the Committee, and correspondence with private citizens and various New Jersey politicians. Topics include finances, elections and organizations.
  - Farmers National Bank, Iowa Church Dedication, 1928; 1930; 1934 (Box 1 (1-Early Political Career), Folder 1)
  - Gabrielson Speeches, 1940; Undated (Box 1 (1-Early Political Career), Folder 2)
  - New Jersey Political Correspondence, 1927-1929 (Box 1 (1-Early Political Career), Folder 3)
  - N.J. State Republican Campaign Committee, 1940 (Box 1 (1-Early Political Career), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings- Willkie Campaign, 1940; Undated (Box 1 (1-Early Political Career), Folder 5)
  - New Jersey Italian American Newspaper Willkie Endorsement, 1940 (Flat-file 1)
  - Photos of Gabrielson, 1943; Undated (Box 1 (1-Early Political Career), Folder 6)
  - Photos of Wendell Willkie's Presidential Campaign, 1940 (Box 1 (1-Early Political Career), Folder 7)
  - Political Correspondence, 1940-1944 (Box 1 (1-Early Political Career), Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, 1925-1929; 1939-1940 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
- Republican National Committee Papers, 1948-1967; 2
  This series includes addresses and statements from Guy George Gabrielson as Republican National Committee Chairman, committee reports, itineraries, committee meeting minutes, campaign materials, regional conference proceedings, official news releases, and printed pamphlets. Topics include the investigation into Gabrielsons ties to Carthage Hydrocol, Inc., state elections, member organizations, such as the Young Republicans, finances, and schools of politics.
  - Addresses and Statements by Chairman Gabrielson, 1949 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 9)
  - Addresses and Statements by Chairman Gabrielson, 1950 January-1950 April (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 10)
  - Addresses and Statements by Chairman Gabrielson, 1950 May-1950 December (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 11-12)
  - Addresses and Statements by Chairman Gabrielson, 1951 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 13-14)
  - Addresses and Statements by Chairman Gabrielson, 1952 January-1952 June (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 15)
  - Bennett, John, 1950 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 16)
  - Budget- Finances, etc., 1950; 1952 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 17)
  - Campaign- Hatch Act, Expenses, etc., 1952 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 18)
  - Campaign Speech Kit, 1950 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 19)
  - Campaign Speech Kit National republican Congressional Committee, 1950 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 20)
  - Capitol Hill Club, 1951; 1961; 1962; 1966; Undated (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 21)
  - Chairman Gabrielson, 1950 February (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 22)
  - Chairman Gabrielson- Personal, 1949-1952 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 23-24)
  - Chairman Gabrielson- Carthage Hydrocol, 1950-1951 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 25)
  - Chairman Gabrielson- Carthage Hydrocol Senate Hearing, 1951 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 26)
  - Chairman Gabrielson Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 27)
  - Chairman Pfeiffer- New York Republican State Committee, 1951 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 28)
  - The Chairman's Letter, 1951 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 29)
  - Condolences, 1950-1951 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 30)
  - Eastern Regional Conference Mayflower Hotel, Washington, D.C, 1951 October 01 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 31)
  - Eastern Regional Republican Conference Planning, 1951 October (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 32)
  - "Editorial Digest", 1950 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 33)
  - Ethnic Origin Division- RNC, 1951-1952 (Box 1 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 34)
  - Executive Committee Chicago, 1950 May (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Meeting and Eastern Seaboard Regional Conference Atlantic City, N.J, 1950 June 23 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Meeting and Western Regional Conference Salt Lake City, 1950 July 31-1950 August 01 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee meeting of the RNC and Eastern Regional Conference Mayflower Hotel, D.C, 1951 October 01 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Meeting RNC Salt Lake City, 1950 July-1950 August (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Washington, D.C, 1950 December 08 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 6)
  - Itineraries, 1949-1951 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 7)
  - Letters Re. Campaign and Election, 1950 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 8)
  - Mailing Lists, 1950 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 9)
  - Material for Letters and Speeches, 1949; Undated (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 10)
  - Meeting- Budget and Finance Committee, 1948-1950 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 11)
  - Meeting- Exec. Committee-RNC Chicago, 1950 May (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 12)
  - Meeting- Exec. Committee-RNC Washington D.C., 1950 December (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 13)
  - Member Lists of State Central Committees, 1951 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 14)
  - Minutes- RNC Washington, D.C, 1951 January (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 15)
  - Missouri Republican Club Certificate, 1949 (Oversized 2, Folder 1)
  - Mock Conventions, 1952; Undated (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 16)
  - National Committee Meeting Chicago, 1950 September 15-1950 September 16 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 17)
  - National Committee Meeting Chicago, 1951 January (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 18)
  - National Federation of Women's Republican Clubs, 1949-1955 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 19-20)
  - "On the Political Front", 1950-1952 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 21)
  - Pro- America, 1942-1943; 1951 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 22)
  - Re- Christmas Cards, 1950-1951 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 23)
  - Regional Conferences Eastern Seaboard, 1950 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 24)
  - Regional Meetings, 1960-1961 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 25)
  - Releases, Biogs, etc., 1949-1952 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 26)
  - Report from George Murphy and Associates Re Go- Party, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 27)
  - Report of the Chairman of the Finance Committee, 1950 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 28)
  - Republican Farm Conference- Sioux City, 1949-1950 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 29-30)
  - RNC, 1951 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 31)
  - RNC, 1952 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 32)
  - RNC Committee Meetings, 1950 (Box 2 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 33)
  - RNC Lists of Officers, Exec. Committee and Members, 1949-1952 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 1)
  - RNC Meeting and Midwestern and Western National Conference Tulsa, 1951 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 2)
  - RNC Meeting and Midwestern and Western National Conference Tulsa, Okla. Gen. Info, 1951 May 11-1951 May 12 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 3)
  - RNC Meeting and Report of Finance Committee San Francisco, 1951-1952 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 4-5)
  - RNC Meeting Chicago, 1952; Undated (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 6)
  - RNC Meeting- Executive Session Washington, D.C., 1951 October (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 7)
  - RNC Meeting Executive Session Washington, D.C, 1951 January (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 8)
  - RNC Meeting Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 9)
  - RNC Meeting San Francisco, 1951-1952 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 10)
  - RNC Meeting San Francisco, 1952 January (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 11-12)
  - RNC Meeting- Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1951 May (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 13)
  - RNC Meeting Washington, D.C., 1949-1950 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 14)
  - RNC Meeting Washington, D.C., 1950 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 15)
  - RNC Meeting Washington, D.C., 1951 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 16)
  - RNC National Farm Conference Sioux City, 1949 September 23 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 17)
  - RNC National Farm Conference Sioux City, 1949 September 24 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 18)
  - RNC News Releases and Publications, 1950-1951; Undated (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 19)
  - RNC Publications- Campaign/Organizations Strategy, 1951; Undated (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 20)
  - RNC Publications- History and Background, 1951-1952; 1967 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 21)
  - RNC Regional Conferences, 1950-1951 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 22)
  - RNC Secretary Mrs. Charles P. Howard, 1949-1952 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 23)
  - RNC Secretary- Mrs. Knowles, 1949 (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 24)
  - School of Politics, 1950; 1950-1952; Undated (Box 3 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 25)
  - Speakers Bureau- Radio/TV, 1950; 1954; Undated (Box 4 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 1)
  - State Elections, 1948-1950 (Box 4 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 2-3)
  - Truman Research, 1951 (Box 4 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 4)
  - Women's Division, 1950-1952 (Box 4 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 5)
  - Women's Federation, 1950; Undated (Box 4 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 6)
  - Young Republicans, 1950-1952 (Box 4 (2-Republican National Committee Papers), Folder 7)
- Republican National Committee 1952 Convention, 1948-1956; 3; 1 Digital Files
  The bulk of this series is a by-product of the exhaustive planning for the 1952 Republican National Convention that nominated General Dwight D. Eisenhower for president. It includes committee reports, correspondence with local businesses, candidate information, the official convention program and campaign materials. Topics include finance, hotels/housing, chaplains, doorkeepers and preparatory actions by various state committees.
  - Applications- General, 1951-1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 8)
  - Assignments, 1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 9)
  - Assistant Chairman, 1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 10)
  - Background Information, 1948; Undated (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 11)
  - California, 1951 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 12)
  - Campaign, 1952; Undated (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 13)
  - Campaign Material, 1950-1952; Undated (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 14)
  - Candidate Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1951-1952; 1956 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 15)
  - Candidate Macarthur, Douglas, 1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 16)
  - Candidate Stassen, Harold, E., 1951-1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 17)
  - Candidate Taft, Robert A., 1951-1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 18)
  - Candidate Warren, Earl, 1951-1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 19)
  - Chairman, Undated (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 20)
  - Chairman- Finance, 1950-1951; Undated (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 21)
  - Chaplains, 1952; Undated (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 22)
  - Chicago Convention Bldg. and International Amphitheatre, 1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 23)
  - Chicago Site Solicitation, Undated (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 24-25)
  - Convent Information/Official Program, 1952; Undated (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 26)
  - Committee on Arrangements, 1950-1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 27)
  - Committee on Arrangements, 1951-1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 28-29)
  - Committee on Arrangements, 1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 30-34)
  - Committee on Arrangements- Mooberg, Henry E., 1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 35)
  - Committee on Arrangements- Report of Housing Subcommittee, 1953; Undated (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 36)
  - Committee on Arrangements San Francisco, 1952 January (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 37)
  - Committee on Arrangements San Francisco Executive Session, 1952 January (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 38)
  - Committee on Arrangements Treasurer, 1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 39)
  - Committee on Call, 1950-1952 (Box 4 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 40)
  - Committee on Call, 1950-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 1)
  - Committee on Contests, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 2)
  - Committee on Resolutions (Platform), 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 3)
  - Committee on Rules, 1948; 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 4)
  - Committee on Site, 1951 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 5)
  - Committee on Site, 1951-1952; Undated (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 6)
  - Committee on Site- Meetings, 1951 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 7)
  - Committee Reports, Undated (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 8)
  - Committees and Subcommittees, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 9)
  - Contest- Florida, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 10)
  - Contest- Georgia, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 11)
  - Contest- Louisiana, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 12)
  - Contests, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 13)
  - Contracts, 1951 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 14)
  - Convention Assignments, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 15)
  - Convention Balloons, Undated (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 16)
  - Convention Prayers, Undated (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 17)
  - Credentials Committee, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 18)
  - Delegates, 1951-1952; Undated (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 19)
  - Doorkeepers, 1952; Undated (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 20)
  - Finance, 1951 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 21)
  - Florida, 1951 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 22)
  - Form Letters, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 23)
  - Hotels, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 24)
  - Housing, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 25)
  - Invitation to Hold 1952 Convention in Philadelphia, Shaped Like a Key, ca. 1950 (Oversized 2, Folder 2)
  - Invitation to Hold 1956 Convention in San Francisco, Including Magazine and Brochures, 1953 (Flat-file 1)
  - Invocations, Undated (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 27)
  - Mississippi, 1951 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 28)
  - Missouri, 1951 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 29)
  - New York, 1951 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 30)
  - Oklahoma, 1951 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 31)
  - Parliamentarians, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 32)
  - Permanent Chairman, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 33)
  - Proxies, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 34)
  - Reapportionment- General, 1951 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 35)
  - Republican National Committee- Nominations, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 36)
  - Resolutions, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 37)
  - Sergeant-at-Arms, 1952; Undated (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 38)
  - Site Committee- Correspondence, 1951 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 39)
  - Subcommittee- Television and Motion Pictures, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 40)
  - Subcommittee- Tickets, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 41)
  - Subcommittee- Music and Decorations, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 42)
  - Subcommittee on Badges, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 43)
  - Subcommittee or Housing- General, 1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 44)
  - Subcommittee on Transportation and Parking, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-Republican National Committee 1952 Convention), Folder 45)